" plays ]
♪ See these eyes of green
♪ I can stare
for a thousand years ♪
♪ Colder than the moon
♪ Well, it's been so long
♪ And I've been
putting out fire ♪
♪ With gasoline
♪ See these eyes of red
♪ Red like jungle
burning bright ♪
♪ Those who feel me near
♪ Pull the blinds
and change their mind ♪
♪ It's been so long
♪ Well, it's been so long
♪ I've been putting out fire
with gasoline ♪
♪ Putting out fire
♪ See these tears of blue
♪ An ageless heart
that can never mend ♪
♪ Tears can never dry
♪ A judgment made
♪ Can never bend
♪ See these eyes so green
♪ I can stare
for a thousand years ♪
♪ Just be still with me
♪ You wouldn't believe
what I've been through ♪
♪ Well, it's been so long
♪ It's been so long
♪ And I've been putting out fire
with gasoline ♪
♪ Putting out fire
♪ With gasoline
♪ 'Cause if you don't know me
well ♪
♪ You had better listen ♪
♪ To the facts about me, baby ♪
♪ That you better know ♪
♪ I'm not one of you ♪
♪ You're not one of me ♪
♪ And the things I see ♪
♪ You may not see ♪
♪ Like, pick up the beat ♪
♪ And close the hand ♪
♪ Check me out, baby ♪
♪ I'm the Mix Match Man ♪
♪ The Mix Match Man ♪
Found it.
Miller.
♪ When I wake up
in the morning, love ♪
♪ And the sunlight hurts
my eyes ♪
♪ And something
without warning, love ♪
♪ Bears heavy on my mind
♪ Then I look at you
♪ And the world's all right
with me ♪
♪ Just one look at you
♪ And I know it's gonna be
♪ A lovely day
- ♪ Lovely day, lovely day
♪ Lovely day, lovely day
- ♪ A lovely day
♪ Lovely day, lovely day,
lovely day, lovely day ♪
♪ When the day
that lies ahead of me ♪
♪ Seems impossible to face
♪ When someone else
instead of me ♪
♪ Always seems to know the way
♪ Then I look at you
♪ And the world's all right
with me ♪
♪ Ah, just want one look
at you ♪
♪ And I know it's gonna be
♪ A lovely day
Yeah.
Yeah?
Yeah!
Yes!
Oh!
♪ Listen to the wind blow
♪ Watch the sun rise
♪ Run in the shadows
♪ Damn your love,
damn your lies ♪
♪ And if you don't love me now
♪ You will never love me again
♪ I can still hear you saying
♪ You would never break
the chain ♪
♪ Never break the chain
♪ And if you don't love me now
- ♪ You don't love me now
♪ You will never love me
again ♪
♪ I can still hear you saying
♪ You would never break
the chain ♪
♪ Never break the chain
♪ Listen to the wind blow
♪ Down comes the night
♪ Run in the shadows
♪ Damn your love,
damn your lies ♪
♪ Break the silence
♪ Damn the dark,
damn the light ♪
♪ And if you don't love me now
♪ You will never love me again
♪ I can still hear you saying
♪ You would never break
the chain ♪
♪ Never break the chain
♪ And if you don't love me now
♪ You don't love me now
♪ You will never love me
again ♪
♪ I can still hear you saying
♪ You would never break
the chain ♪
♪ Never break the chain
♪ And if you don't love me
now ♪
♪ You don't love me now
♪ You will never love me
again ♪
♪ I can still hear you saying
♪ You would never break
the chain ♪
♪ Never break the chain
♪ Chains
♪ Keep us together
♪ Running in the shadows
♪ Chains
♪ Keep us together
♪ Running in the shadows
♪ Chains
♪ Keep us together
♪ Running in the shadows
♪ Chains
I loved you!
♪ To get off, to get off
♪ To get off, to get, get off
♪ Looking through that dress
drive me crazy and makes me ♪
♪ Get off
♪ Sensuality excites my mind,
it makes me ♪
♪ Get off
♪ If I were you, I'd get
a good perspective on how to ♪
♪ Get off
- Don't fucking touch me.
Hey.
♪ Love me wild
Ow! Fucker!
♪ Get off
♪ Tie me up at your place,
I can love you crazy ♪
♪ In the heat,
you will understand ♪
♪ Danger and excitement,
that's what makes a lady ♪
♪ Find out what she wants
in a man ♪
♪ To get off, to get off
Let's go.
♪ To get off
- Ow!
- ♪ To get off
- gtt
♪ Ooh-ooh! Ooh-ooh!
Ooh-ooh! Ooh-ooh! ♪
Fuck you!
Stop!
Yeah!
♪ Get off
Aah! Aah!
♪ Doing all right
♪ A little jiving
on a Saturday night ♪
♪ And come what may
♪ Gonna dance the day away
♪ Jenny was sweet
♪ She always smiled
for the people she'd meet ♪
♪ On trouble and strife ♪
♪ She had another way
of looking at life ♪
♪ The news is blue
- ♪ The news is blue
♪ It has its own way
to get to you ♪
- ♪ Ooh, ooh
- ♪ What can I do?
♪ What can I do?
♪ I'll never remember
my time with you ♪
♪ Pick up your feet
♪ Got to move to the trick
of the beat ♪
♪ There is no elite
♪ Just take your place
in the driver's seat ♪
♪ Driver's seat
♪ Ooh, ooh
♪ Yeah
♪ We're doing all right
♪ Ooh, ooh
♪ A little jiving
on a Saturday night ♪
♪ Yeah
♪ And come what may
♪ Ooh, ooh
♪ Gonna dance the day away
♪ Yeah
♪ Driver's seat
♪ Ooh, ooh
♪ Yeah
♪ Jenny was sweet
♪ Ooh, ooh
♪ There is no elite
♪ You got to see I got to go ♪
♪ 'Cause you know ♪
♪ That would be a lie ♪
♪ I just can't keep it all
inside ♪
♪ I wasn't trying
to keep you down ♪
♪ But I'd like
to keep you around ♪
♪ 'Cause you know ♪
♪ I just can't keep it all
inside ♪
♪ And you can take me
for a ride ♪
♪ But if you want me,
just lay low ♪
♪ And make me stay
when I should go ♪
♪ I might not talk,
but still you try ♪
♪ Because it's in me,
we know ♪
♪ And you know ♪
♪ I just can't keep it all
inside ♪
♪ So you can take me
for a ride ♪
♪ But if you want me,
just lay low ♪
♪ And make me stay...♪
- Hello.
- ♪ ...when I should go ♪
Hi.
♪ Ooh
♪ It's so good, it's so good,
it's so good ♪
♪ It's so good, it's so good
♪ Ooh
♪ Heaven knows, heaven knows,
heaven knows ♪
♪ Heaven knows, heaven knows
♪ Ooh
♪ I feel love, I feel love,
I feel love ♪
♪ I feel love, I feel love
♪ I feel love
♪ ...joy
♪ Gonna have
a merry Christmas ♪
♪ It'll be the real McCoy
♪ We've got things to prepare
♪ Let there be loving
♪ Let us care
♪ Gonna be a merry Christmas
with magic in the air ♪
♪ We can meet
under the mistletoe ♪
♪ Doo-wa, doo-wa, ooh-wa
♪ And we can always hope
there might be snow, oh, oh ♪
♪ Santa Claus is on his way
♪ So prepare for Christmas Day
♪ Let's have a merry Christmas
Want to mind your own business?
Huh?
Merry fuckin' Christmas.
♪ Ring, Christmas bells,
merrily ring ♪
♪ Tell all the world
Jesus is king ♪
♪ Ring, Christmas bells,
toll loud and long ♪
♪ Your message sweet
heal and prolong ♪
♪ Come, all you people,
join in the singing ♪
♪ Repeat the story
told by the ringing ♪
♪ Ring, ring, ring, ring
♪ Ring, Christmas bells,
throughout the earth ♪
♪ Tell of the news
of Jesus' birth ♪
♪ Loudly proclaim
with one accord ♪
♪ The happy tale
♪ Welcome the Lord
♪ Ring, Christmas bells,
merrily ring ♪
♪ Tell all the world
Jesus is king ♪
♪ Ring
♪ Ring Christmas bells,
merrily ring ♪
♪ Tell all the world
Jesus is king ♪
♪ Loudly proclaim
with one accord ♪
♪ The happy tale
♪ Welcome the Lord
♪ Ring, Christmas bells,
sound far and near ♪
♪ The birthday of Jesus
is here ♪
♪ Herald the news
to old and young ♪
♪ Tell it to all
in every tongue ♪
♪ Ring, ring, ring, ring
♪ Ring
♪ Ahh
Yo.
Fuck off, man.
Oh!
♪ The wind blew some luck
in my direction ♪
♪ I caught it in my hands
today ♪
♪ I finally made
a tricky French connection ♪
♪ You winked and gave me
your okay ♪
♪ I'll take you on a trip
beside the ocean ♪
♪ And drop the top
at Chesapeake Bay ♪
♪ Ain't nothing like
a scattered dose of ocean ♪
♪ The moon will send you
on your way ♪
♪ Moonlight
♪ Feels right
♪ We'll lay back and observe
the constellations ♪
♪ And watch the moon
smiling bright ♪
♪ I'll play the radio
on Southern stations ♪
♪ 'Cause Southern belles
are hell at night ♪
♪ You say you came to Baltimore
from Ole Miss ♪
♪ A class of '74 gold ring
♪ The eastern moon looks ready
for a wet kiss ♪
♪ To make the tide rise again
♪ Moonlight
♪ Feels right
Hey!
♪ We'll see the sun come up
on Sunday morning ♪
♪ And watch it fade the moon
away ♪
♪ I guess you know
I'm giving you a warning ♪
♪ 'Cause me and moon
are itching to play ♪
♪ I'll take you on a trip
beside the ocean ♪
♪ And drop the top
at Chesapeake Bay ♪
♪ Ain't nothing like
a scattered dose of ocean ♪
♪ The moon will send you
on your way ♪
♪ Moonlight
♪ Feels right
Hey.
Whoa.
I'm just playing, man.
♪ Nights in white satin
♪ Never reaching the end
♪ Letters I've written
♪ Never meaning to send
♪ Beauty I've always missed
♪ With these eyes before
♪ Just what the truth is
♪ I can't say any more
♪ 'Cause I love you
♪ Yes, I love you
♪ Oh, how I love you
♪ Oh
♪ Gazing at people
♪ Some hand in hand
♪ Just what I'm going through
♪ They can't understand
♪ Some try to tell me ♪
♪ Thoughts they cannot defend
♪ Just what you want to be
♪ You will be in the end
♪ And I love you
♪ Yes, I love you
♪ Oh, how I love you
♪ Nights in white satin
♪ Never reaching the end
♪ Letters I've written
♪ Never meaning to send
♪ Beauty I've always missed
♪ 'Cause I love you
♪ Yes, I love you
♪ Oh, how I love you
♪ Oh
♪ 'Cause I love you
♪ Yes, I love you
♪ Oh, how I love you
♪ Lila came the day
I heard it thunder ♪
♪ Lila ♪
♪ There she was,
just a-standing by herself ♪
♪ When she came,
she brought me flowers ♪
♪ And, baby...♪
Oh!
Oh! Fuck!
Aah!
Whoa.
I loved her.
I still do.
♪ Dear friend,
if you want to feel better ♪
♪ Don't let the devil
make you toss this letter ♪
♪ If you've been crossed up
by hoodoo-voodoo ♪
♪ A wizard or the lizard
♪ If you got family trouble,
man trouble, woman trouble ♪
♪ No light through the tunnel
♪ If you're looking for
a true friend or a true lover ♪
♪ Or if you've been living
undercover ♪
♪ Well, I'm coming to your town
to break it all down ♪
♪ And help you
with all of this ♪
♪ I'm looking to help you
find bliss one day or one way ♪
♪ Can't miss
♪ I'm here to tear all the walls
down ♪
♪ Doesn't matter if it's
a large town or a small town ♪
♪ Just like Joshua and
the fabled walls of Jericho ♪
♪ I'm here to tear down
the institution ♪
♪ God spoke to me,
said, "Listen to me ♪
♪ I anoint you with the power
that'll get 'em all movin'" ♪
♪ You're agitated,
you've prayed and meditated ♪
♪ You're concentrated
on getting elevated ♪
♪ By sundown Monday
♪ You who come will be blessed
with a big money blessing ♪
♪ You will be doubted
by all the unbelievers ♪
♪ And all of the friends
I'm addressing ♪
♪ But you must tell
seven friends ♪
♪ You must first bring
♪ And don't be selfish
and keep this all to yourself ♪
♪ And don't eat shellfish
♪ Hate is trying to take someone
else's love for yourself ♪
♪ But I'm here to tell you
♪ That love is trying to help
someone else ♪
♪ I realize that you have tried
and tried ♪
♪ And are just about ready
to give up ♪
♪ But I got good news for you
♪ God has spoken to my mind
and told me to tell you ♪
♪ To get moving in the right
direction for a change ♪
♪ I'm gonna put you
in the fast lane! ♪
♪ You need to see me right away
so I can fix this-ah ♪
♪ You need to see me
right away ♪
♪ You need to see me right away
so I can fix this-ah ♪
♪ You need to see me
right about now ♪
♪ God of Seven, open up
the windows of heaven ♪
♪ And pour out a rich
and mighty blessing ♪
♪ Not on his town or her town,
but your town ♪
♪ Are you ready
for the message? ♪
♪ I have a special
financial blessing ♪
♪ That once I have placed
in your hand ♪
♪ Yeah, I want you to begin
using this blessing ♪
♪ On the very first day
that you can ♪
♪ And if you are suffering
a strange sickness-ah ♪
♪ Or someone is blocking up
all of your success-ah ♪
♪ You need to see me right away
so I can fix this-ah ♪
Signed sincerely, yours
in faith, love, and peace,
your friend Archbishop
Harold Holmes.